In this exercise, you'll be asked to create an RDS database with backups enabled and then
在此练习中 将要求您创建启用了备份的 RDS 数据库 然后
restore that database to a point in time to demonstrate a point in time recovery.
将该数据库复原到时间点以演示时间点恢复
Let's take a quick look at how to create this database.
让我们快速了解如何创建此数据库
Within AWS, we go into RDS and we create a database.
在 AWS 中 我们进入 RDS 并创建数据库
RDS will ask us,
RDS 会问我们
we want a standard or easy create.
我们想要一个标准或简单的创造
Doesn't make a whole lot difference, we'll say standard.
不会有很大的差别 我们会说标准
We are going to create a MySQL database,
我们要创建一个 MySQL 数据库
scroll through a fair number of options.
滚动浏览一个公平的选项
You can say dev test,
你可以说 dev 测试
just so that we have a simpler database.
所以我们有一个更简单的数据库
We can leave most of these settings as they are for this exercise.
我们可以把大部分这些设置留给他们来做
We'll choose a burstable class just to
我们会选择一个
save some money because the larger classes will cost more money.
省点钱 因为大班会花更多的钱
Then as we scroll all the way down,
当我们往下滚动时
we'll see that there is some additional configuration.
我们会发现还有一些额外的配置
In the additional configuration,
在附加配置中
I just want to make sure that backups are in fact enabled, which is the default.
我只想确保备份实际上已启用 这是缺省值
Now with the automatic backups enabled,
现在启用了自动备份
this is what enables us to actually do the point in time recovery.
这才使得我们能够真正做到时间点恢复
Which is why this is very important for this exercise,
所以这对这次演习很重要
to make sure that this checkbox is in fact checked.
以确保此复选框实际上已选中
From there, we'll create our database.
从那里 我们将创建我们的数据库